Despite all of the damage that it's caused,
the shutdown has been, you know, pretty damaging.
I mean, it's not yet because it's early,
but it gets a little bit worse as it goes along.
And we'll be making cuts that will be permanent.
And we're only gonna cut Democrat programs.
I hate to tell you. I guess that makes sense.
But we're only cutting Democrat programs.
We'll be cutting some very popular Democrat programs
that aren't popular with Republicans, frankly,
because that's the way it works.
They wanted to do this,
so we'll give them a little taste of their own medicine.
But Chuck Schumer proclaimed this morning
that every day gets better for them.
No, every day, it's actually getting worse for them.
And they're having a rebellion in the Democrat Party.